

[
    {
        "category": "Colours",
        "question": "Which colours is a banana",
        "answers": [
            "white", "black", "green", "yellow"
        ],
        "correct": [2,3]
    },
    {
        "category": "Math",
        "question": "What is 5*5?",
        "answers": [
            "25", "26", "10", "35"
        ],
        "correct": [0]

    },
    {
    "category": "IT",
        "question": "Who is Bill Gates?",
        "answers": [
            "A random person", "Founder of Microsoft", "Founder of the keyboard", "The person who invented internet"
        ],
        "correct": [1]
    },
    {
        "category": "Schools",
            "question": "What is Nackademin?",
            "answers": [
                "A school", "The swedish nationalteam areana", "A pub located in Stockholm", "The carmodel name on the new Volvo?"
            ],
            "correct": [0]
        },
        {
            "category": "Food and drinks",
                "question": "What is PUB short for?",
                "answers": [
                    "Public club", "Public bar", "Public house", "Public Bistro"
                ],
                "correct": [3]
            },
            {
                "category": "Animals",
                    "question": "Which of these animals is related to the catfamily",
                    "answers": [
                        "Giraff", "Lion", "Fish", "Tiger"
                    ],
                    "correct": [1,3]
                },
                {
                    "category": "Carmodels",
                        "question": "What carbrand was created in japan?",
                        "answers": [
                            "Volvo", "Fiat", "Toyota", "Lexus"
                        ],
                        "correct": [1]
                    },
                    {
                        "category": "Animals",
                            "question": "What animal is called the king of the forest in Sweden?",
                            "answers": [
                                "Moose", "Fish", "Hawk", "Cow"
                            ],
                            "correct": [0]
                        },
                        {
                            "category": "Drinks",
                                "question": "Which of these drinks is a beer?",
                                "answers": [
                                    "G&T", "Redbull/Vodka", "Åbro 10,2", "Skinnybitch"
                                ],
                                "correct": [2]
                            },
                            {
                                "category": "Capital",
                                    "question": "What city is the capital of Sweden",
                                    "answers": [
                                        "Stockholm", "Malmö", "Göteborg", "Gotland"
                                    ],
                                    "correct": [0]
                                }
                
]


